libertyfirstnews.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Liberty One News

**Last Updated 8/25/2017  
Version 1.0**

If you require additional information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contactus@libertyonetv.com.

At Liberty One Broadcasting. (“L1B”), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by L1B and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, L1B makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We will not disclose your individual identity or personal data to any party.

When we do present information to outside companies it will be in an aggregate fashion, that will prevent the company from identifying you or contacting you.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information, please contact us at contactus@libertyonetv.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
L1B does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, and customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on L1B.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Third Party Advertisers**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display the advertisements and links that appear on L1B. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

L1B has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. L1B’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Subscription to our Email List**  
After signing up to receive regular updates from L1B by e-mail, depending on which website you subscribe to, users will begin to receive a brief synopsis of current news events, or other digital content, available on Liberty One News (http://libertyonenews.com), American Journal (http://americanjournalreview.com), Daily Presser (http://www.dailypresser.com) and LibertyOneTV (http://www.libertyonetv.com)  (collectively, the “Sites”) delivered on a daily or weekly basis. Additionally, users may receive other announcements from L1B. We collect subscriber’s e-mail addresses in order to distribute our updates and announcements and do not otherwise share them with other companies or partners. L1B respects your right to privacy of the personal information you provide us on our site. Unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide will not be known to any other party except you and L1B. This policy is intended to explain how your personal information is collected and how it will be treated.

Users can choose to unsubscribe from any of L1B’s email lists at any time by following the unsubscribe procedures found at the bottom of each e-mail.
